During the day, doctors arrive,
they have a mobile
X-ray machine,
there is equipment there
to check the heart.
Within half a day, basically,
any person undergoes
the medical examination.
For example,
my brother's quite advanced
varicose veins did not
become a reason
to
give him a deferment,
although for this Wednesday,
that is, for tomorrow,
he has a surgery scheduled,
a doctor from Kherson will come and
should operate on him.
But because
the surgery is planned,
this, like,
most likely,
did not interest the doctors
at the medical examination at all.
When problems with this leg
will start for him,
nobody knows.
Because he delayed
this surgery for a long time,
now the leg looks
very bad.
And,
damn,
humanely they should have let him
at least just do
this surgery.
Or let them do it.
But instead they are preparing him
for an obstacle course, even though
he has had a fever for two days.